Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Dairy Queen Blizzard flavors,
but lower in calories and higher in
protein. This is the Snow Drift
Blizzard. Let me show you how to make
it. Even Dairy Queen would approve.
Tastes just like Lucky Charms.
>> If you're wondering why you've never
heard of this Blizzard, that's because
it's not even out yet. But Dairy Queen
leaked their January Blizzard flavors,
so we're recreating them before they
even drop. So, the Snowdrift Blizzard is
a blue cake batter base with an Oreo
swirl and a marshmallow swirl. So
obviously it's going to be amazing and
if it's anything like this version, it
might be the best pler they've ever come
out with. By the way, the recipe for the
base will be down below in the
description along with all the other
instructions. A few tips for this recipe
in particular. I like to freeze the
Oreos for about 15 to 20 minutes before
using them as mixins. This helps them
not get absolutely pulverized when you
use the mixing setting. And for the
marshmallow swirl, you can use fluff or
as you weird people call it, marshmallow
cream, but I prefer these little
jet-puffed bits. They're little like
Lucky Charm style marshmallows and
they're just the perfect texture for ice
cream.